Hi, I'm Stan DeFreitas, Mr. Green Thumb.
This is a Mother-In-Law's tongue, sometimes called Sansevieria.
And the Mother-In-Law's Tongue, well you kind of get the idea where the name came from.
It looks like a long tongue.
This plant is one of those succulent kind of plants that's really tough.
This is almost a brown thumber's favorite plant.
You really have to try to kill this plant once it's established.
Probably not that cold hardy, but this plant sometimes called say Mother-In-Law's Tongue or it used to be called hemp plant as well.
They used to grow this plant and they would actually peel the leaves and make a type of hemp rope from it also.
A little trivia that you may not have known.
As far as the plant goes, it grows well in a good, peaty type soil, but you can grow it in just about anything; sand, rocky, it doesn't matter.
This plant will survive.
This plant can be grown inside in a bright area or even a low lit area.
The plant still seems to survive.
Good water soluble plant food maybe once every two to three months should be fine, or you can add some extra fertilizer at planting time.
Sansevieria, good plant if you're trying to make sure the plant won't die.
For On Gardening I'm Stan DeFreitas, Mr. Green Thumb.